

# Alla Nesterova

## **Experience**

2015 — now

Chief accountant • Artificial Core

2014 — 2015

Chief accountant • Pershiy tsentr terapiyi ta mikrohirurgiyi oka

2012 - 2013

Accountant • KESZ

2011 - 2012

Accountant • Park Kino

+380 96 497-99-67





# **Education**

# **Sumy State University**

2008 — 2011

Faculty of Electronics and Informational Technologies

#### **ACCA**

2016

• Diploma of International Financial Reporting

# SkillUp

2019

Front-end development

## Online resources

**2018** — **2019** 

Codacademy, Stepik, ITDV, Prometheus, Hubr and others

### Skills

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React/Redux

#### **About**

I started my career in finances. I'm diligent, reliable, responsible, friendly and always try to do more than is expected of me. That allowed me to occupy chief accountant position in the last two companies I worked for. My collaboration with the latest company led me to realization that I want to be a software engineer. I like when everything is in its place and works as expected. I like to automate processes. And be a valuable member of a team that works on an engaging goal. Thank you for taking your time reading this. Hope I'll meet you in person.